邓菲女议员  请问你如何回应
Councilwoman Dunphy, how do you respond
外界认为你穿着新套装性感非凡的观点
to allegations that you look super sexy in your new suit?
我还没当选呢
Uh, I haven't been elected yet.
快点  孩子们  我们得去投票了
Come on, kids! We gotta vote!
-亲爱的  拜托你别拍了  -人家太兴奋了嘛
- Honey, come on. Please stop filming. - I'm just excited!
从今以后  你就要当上女议员了
After today, you are going to be a councilwoman,
而我则会成为第一丈夫
and I am going to be a first husband.
你要是再不停拍
And if you don't stop filming,
你就将成为我的前一任丈夫了
you're going to be my first husband.
好了  大伙儿都赶紧的
All right, everybody, come on!
你们记住自己的职责了吗  孩子们
Do you know what you're doing, kids?
你们几个负责电话银行[电话联络选民拉票]
You guys are manning the phone banks.
艾丽克斯  你是他们的头儿
Alex, you're in charge of that.
凭什么该她当头儿啊  什么是电话银行啊
Wh-why is she in charge? And what's--what's a phone bank?
这就是原因
That's why.
-菲尔  -我知道
- Phil. - I got it.
我负责接送50名十佳老人去投票站
I will be driving 50 of our finest senior citizens to the polls,
当然  前提是  他们还能记得这件事
assuming, of course, that they remember that I'm coming for them.
-"你这是在哪儿呀"  -说得好
- Where you at? - High-five.
老年人就爱忘事
Old people occasionally forget things.
好了  各位  我们出发吧  出发吧
Okay. All right, everybody, let's go. Let's go.
等等等等等等  马上就好
Wait, wait, wait, wait, wait! Real quick!
抱歉  大家都围过来  快点
Sorry. Everybody get in there. Jump in there.
我要说的是  我们为你倍感骄傲
I just want to say how proud of you we all are.
你就是鼓舞人心的榜样
You're an inspiration.
谁能想到20年前
Who would have thought that 20 years ago
当你正值青春大好年华时
when you were still in the bloom of your youth--
够了  我要去开车了
Okay, I'm gonna go start the car.
克莱尔喜欢争强好胜
Claire likes to win.
她8岁时  一个参加女童子军的朋友
When she was 8, a little girl scout friend of hers
吹嘘自己能卖出最多的饼干
bragged she could sell the most cookies.
结果克莱尔挨家挨户推销
Damn if Claire didn't walk the neighborhood
走到脚板起泡  比她多卖了10盒饼干
till she got blisters on her feet and won by ten boxes.
最精彩之处是
Best part is
克莱尔甚至都不是女童子军
Claire wasn't even a girl scout.
克莱尔  您的用心之选
The choice is Claire!
镇议员选举  请投克莱尔・邓菲一票
Vote Claire Dunphy for town council.
爱死这个了
Aw, I love it!
-怎么样  -我太喜欢了
- What do you think, huh? - I love it.
我们从克莱格分类广告网站上买的
We got it on Craigslist.
原本是小贩吆喝玉米饼的
Came off a taco truck.
-真的  -我很感激你们为我做的一切
- It did. - I love that you're doing this for me.
-多谢了  -没事
- Thank you! - You're welcome.
我知道克莱尔把输赢看得有多重要
I know how important winning is to Claire.
而我又喜欢装饰打扮
And I love to festoon things.
我们就是她的梦之队
We're her dream team.
所以我们专门腾出今天  送莉莉去学校后
So we cleared the whole day, dropped Lily off at school,
马上就去投票了
and voted first thing.
尽管某人"基"情爆发  难以自控
Although, uh, one of us had a bit of a dimpled chad situation.
能请你再演示一次如何使用这机器吗  基德
Can you tell me how this machine works again, Chad?
当然  没问题
Oh, sure. No problem.
我就看一眼  就看一眼
Just wanna look in here. Just--
摩登家庭
第三季 第十九集
谢了  谢了
Thank you. Thank you.
-再见  再见  -有劳了各位
- Bye! Bye!- Thank you, guys!
我"克"以肯定杜恩输定了
I can see Clairely now that Duane is gone.
再见  谢了  我的妈呀
Bye! Thank you! Oh, my gosh.
行了  大伙儿快上车  出发  出发
Okay, everybody, get in the car. Let's go. Let's go.
祝你好运  克莱尔
Good luck today, Claire.
劳莉  谢谢你
Oh, Laurie, thank you.
随带一提  我们家有天大的好消息
Hey, by the way, we have some really good news.
-怎么了  -贝琦被俄勒冈州大学录取了
- What's that? - Becky got into the University of Oregon.
恭喜了
Oh, congratulations!
你有什么消息吗  海莉
Any news, Haley?
暂  暂时还  还没有
Uh, uh, no, not-- not yet,
不过  真为你感到开心呢
but, you know, super psyched!
等待录取的过程就如同一场噩梦
This whole waiting-to-hear thing has been a nightmare
从收到第一封回信开始就缠绕着我
since the very first letter.
我太紧张了  我不敢看
I'm too nervous. I can't do it.
亲爱的邓菲小姐
"Dear miss Dunphy,
我们抱歉地通知你
we regret to inform you..."
然后呢  别吊我胃口啊
What?! Don't leave me hanging!
从那以后  我决定只把好消息带回家
After that, I decided to only tell my parents good news.
就只剩一所学校没回信了
I have one school left,
而我唯一收到的好消息
and the only good news I've gotten
就是我那烦死人的邻居贝琦
is that my annoying neighbor Becky
要搬去俄勒冈了
is moving back east to Oregon.
-曼尼  拿笔记下来  -我身上没带笔
- Manny, write this down. - I didn't bring a pen.
选举日就是美国最辉煌的时刻
Election day is America at its finest.
人民当家做主  政府俯首听命
The people speak, and the government listens.
我不知道你们哥伦比亚是怎么运作的
I don't know what they do in Colombia.
鬼才晓得  别问了
No one does, and don't ask.
虽说投票本身就是一项特权
I mean, we know that voting's a privilege,
可当选票上出现我女儿的名字时
but for my daughter to have her name on that ballot,
意义就特别重大了
it just means so much more--
算了  我还是晚点再投票吧
You know what? I think I'm gonna vote later.
为什么  你要去哪里啊
What? Where are you going?
队伍排太长了
Ah, the line is too long.
就3个人而已  而且又没人带枪
It's only three people! And nobody has a gun!
我们在这里  我叫克莱尔
We're here, we're Claire,
接受这个事实吧
get used to it!
我不确定那口号能让人记得住
You know, I'm not sure if that's tracking.
来  让我试一试
Here, let me try one.
无需千里眼  也"克"看出"莱"该选谁
You don't have to be Clairevoyant to know who to vote for.
镇议员选举  请投邓菲一票
Vote Dunphy for town council.
是克莱尔・邓菲
Uh, uh, uh, Claire Dunphy.
她名叫克莱尔
Uh, C-Caire's her first name.
抱歉我说得不太清"克"[楚]
I'm sorry if that wasn't Claire.
我的天  你看  明明眼前就是垃圾桶
Oh, my God. Look at that. There's a trash can right there,
那男的还随手乱丢废纸
and that guy just threw his paper on the sidewalk.
喂  穿黄夹克的那个
Hey! You in the yellow jacket.
捡起来  丢进垃圾桶里
Pick it up and put it in the trash.
-我的妈呀  他还真照做了  -是的
- Oh, my God. He did it. - Yes, he did.
来  让我试一下
Ooh, here. Let me try one.I'll try...
喂  龙纹身的女孩  不要随意乱穿马路
Hey, dragon tattoo, no jaywalking!
亲娘啊
oh, my gosh.
小喇叭真有威力
This is an instrument of power.
用来卖玉米饼怎么就不畅销呢
How could they not sell tacos?
你知道我们可以怎样利用这玩意吗
You know what we could do with this thing?
小卡  我们绝对可以造福社会啊
Cam, we could really make a difference.
我们可以化身为"改变之声"
We could be the voice of change.
我懂了
Ooh, I got it!
立刻去那家弄丢我衬衫的干洗店吼吼看
Let's go yell at the dry cleaner that lost my shirt.
快过来  伙伴
Come on, gang.
今天邓菲一家要全力出击
Today is the Dunphys at their best.
我是《每周救星》报的记者  介意我
I'm from the "Weekly Saver." Mind if I ask you
-问几个有关选举的问题吗  -随便问
- a couple questions about the big election? - Not at all.
向我开炮吧
Fire away.
你今天会投谁一票呢
Who are you voting for today?
克莱尔・邓菲
Claire Dunphy.
总算听到有人提这名字了
Finally. I've been waiting for someone to say that name.
为什么
Why?
因为在下就是克莱尔・邓菲
Uh... Because I am Claire Dunphy.
抱歉  我是从广告营销部调过来的
Oh, sorry. They moved me over from ad sales.
我们轮流报道新闻
We take turns reporting.
你对于今天的胜算有多大把握
How do you feel about your chances today?
比我几分钟之前预想的要差了很多
Not as good as I did a few minutes ago.
不  她信心满满
No, she feels great.
志在必得  全家人都志在必得
Um, her spirits are high. The whole family's high.
-拿去编头条新闻吧  -菲尔  别
- There's your headline. - Phil, no.
来张全家福怎么样
Uh, how about a photo of all of you?
-当然没问题  -妈妈  标签
- Yeah. Sure. Yes. - Mom, mom, mom. Tag.
-衣服标签还在呢  -我的天
- Tag's still on. - Oh, my Goodness.
谢了
Thank you.
不然拍照可就尴尬了  好
That would have been a really awkward picture. Okay.
天啊
No!
那是什么啊
What is that?
是牙齿吗
Is that a tooth?
-好恶  -太强悍了
- Ew! - Awesome!
你都多大了
How old are you? No!
-再来一次  -怎么会这样啊
- Do it again! - How does that even happen?
以前溜冰时摔的  就装了颗假牙
It's a-a fake tooth from an old ice-skating injury.
-现在松脱了  -天呐  干嘛非得是今天啊
- It just fell out. - Oh, my gosh. Why today?!
-怎么办啊  -别大惊小怪
- What about the... - Let's not overreact.
-让我看看  -好吧  好
- Let's--let me see it. - Okay. All right.
拍好了  谢谢
Got it. Thanks.
你刚刚怎么了
What happened back there?
太多人排队  我懒得等
Line was too long. I couldn't wait.
你买冰沙还等过45分钟呢
I've seen you wait 45 minutes in line for sherbet!
那是因为我喜欢吃冰沙  行吗
Well, I happen to like sherbet, okay?
我带你去的那地方
That place I take you
有全西海岸最好吃的冰沙
has the greatest sherbet on the west coast.
他们有柠檬冰沙  椰子冰沙
They got lime sherbet, they got coconut sherbet.
怎么聊到冰沙去了
Why are we talking about sherbet?
他明显是在转移话题
He's clearly changing the subject.
你怎么没上学啊
Why aren't you in school?
他又转移话题了
He's doing it again.
曼尼说得对  你就像只"阿迪亚"
Manny's right. You're being very ardilla.
-"阿迪亚"  -没错  就是那种
- "Ardilla"? - Yeah, you know, the--
就是那什么
The one that--that--
-兔子吗  我像兔子吗  -不  不是
- Rabbit? I was being rabbit-y? - No, another one
-是大脸蛋  大尾巴的  -花栗鼠吗
- With the cheeks and the tail and... - Chipmunk?
-负鼠吗  -她说的明显是松鼠
- Possum? -Okay, obviously she means squirrel.
你之前"古怪如松鼠"
You were being squirrely then,
-现在也是"古怪如松鼠"  -总比像老鼠好
- You're being squirrely now. - Better than being a rat.
曼尼  让我和他谈谈
Manny, give us a minute.
当然好  我毫不费力就戳穿了他
Oh, sure. I served him up on a silver platter.
怎么了
What?
好吧  没什么大不了的
All right, it's no big deal.
有个女人在那儿工作
There was a woman working there.
我不想让她见到我
I didn't want her to see me.
-她是谁  -她叫多蒂
- Who is she? - Her name is Dottie.
她是我离婚后的第一任女友
She's the first woman I dated after my divorce.
你跟迪迪离婚后勾搭上了多蒂
You dated a Dottie after Dede?
你搞错重点了
Y-you're focusing on the wrong thing here.
重点是  我和她不是好聚好散的
The--the point is it ended badly.
我试图和平分手  可是
I tried to let her down easy, but, uh,
她没能坦然接受
she didn't take it too well.
其实  我也不知道她是怎么接受的
Actually, I don't know how she took it,
因为我没看见
'cause I wasn't there.
我们谈了几周恋爱  然后就  你懂的
We dated a few weeks, then after we... You know,
我趁她没醒  从她家偷偷溜了
I slipped out of her house before she woke up
再也没联系过她
and never called her again.
我把裤子扔在她家院子  把汽车挂的空挡
Put my pants on in her yard, put the car in neutral,
使之缓缓驶出车道  车灯都没敢打开
let it roll down the driveway, lights off.
哎呀  可耻历史我说不下去了
Hey, I can't talk about this anymore.
所以就因为那个女人
So because of this woman,
你没给你女儿投票
you didn't vote for your daughter?
那是克莱尔啊  我们要让她赢
It's Claire! We need her to win!
我可不希望她肺都气炸掉  把怒火都撒在我们头上
I don't want to be around when something that tight comes unraveled.
我会想办法的
I'll figure out something.
也许工作人员是轮班的
Maybe those poll workers take shifts.
别胆小地躲在自己的窝里
Stop hiding in your little cave like a--
像那啥一样  那什么...
Like, you know. Like the-- the--the--
-别再让我猜了  -不是
- I really don't wanna do this again. - No, the--
不不不  那种大家伙  浑身长毛的
No. No. The big one, like, uh, the monster furry one.
唉  我怎么老是记不住动物名字
Ay, why can't I remember any animal names?
欢迎乘坐邓菲快车
Climb aboard the Dunphy Express.
下一站――民主
Next stop--democracy.
-别  别  -请留步
- Well--no, no... - Please don't go.
我保证  不再开玩笑了
I won't do that anymore. I promise.
对了  我们半路停一下
Oh. Uh, we need to make a quick stop.
我要取我的新眼镜
I gotta pick up my new glasses.
不行啊  我...
No can do. I, uh...
还有很多人等着我呢
I got a lot of people waitin', so...
就两分钟而已
It'll just take two minutes.
没有眼镜  我连选票都看不清
I can't even see the ballot without my glasses.
我要是投错了票
I mark the wrong box,
新一届议会就会叫我和男人结婚了
next thing you know I'll be married to a guy.
允许同性婚姻  不代表强制同性结婚  沃特
Yeah, I-- I don't think it's mandatory, Walt.
我跳舞风度翩翩  基佬们不会放过我的
I'm a good dancer. They'll come for me.
必须的
Oh, yeah.
他们会把你的衣服扣子弄坏
They will break all your buttons...
然后说你们送来时就是这样
and say you brought it in that way.
好  快跑  快跑
Okay, go, go, go!
世间不平事太多  正好趁机泄私愤
Turns out we had a lot of axes to grind.
而且装备齐全  所以我俩就玩个不停了
And a hybrid, so there was virtually no stopping us.
别看那电影
Do not see that movie!
那电影会让你哭笑不得
You will neither laugh nor cry!
"全市最棒披萨"
"Best pizza in the city"?
其实连"全街最棒"都算不上
Not even the best pizza on this street.
宣传照上的发型根本不是在这家店做的
They do not do the hair of the people on those pictures!
"完全免费检查"
"Totally free checking"?
别做梦了
Don't bank on it!
好了  刚刚很好玩
Okay, that was really fun,
但我们得回去帮克莱尔拉票了
But now we gotta go back to campaigning for Claire.
这话我们说了两小时了
We've been saying that for two hours.
没错  但现在我是说真的
Yes, but now I-I really mean it.
-天呐  那是桑迪  -桑德拉・布洛克吗[名演员]
- Oh, my god, there's Sandy! - Sandra Bullock?
是啊  桑德拉・布洛克
Yeah, Sandra Bullock.
我和她是好朋友  所以我叫她桑迪
We're such good friends, I call her "Sandy," So...
逗你的  是莉莉幼儿园的桑迪啦
No, Sandy who works at Lily's preschool.
-她在那儿  -哦  对
- Right there. - Oh, yeah.
-你知道吗  她订婚了  -不是吧
- You know, she got engaged. - No!
-跟她那基佬男友吗  -是啊
- To the gay boyfriend? - Totally.
不是吧  她怎么没看出来啊
Oh, how does she not see it?
要是我男朋友也那么帅
If I was with somebody that gorgeous,
我也不会在乎他的"口味"了
I'd overlook a few quirks, too.
首先  谢谢夸奖
First of all, thank you.
其次
Second of all...
说得太有道理了
point well taken.
唉  可怜的桑迪啊  真替她伤心
I don't know. Poor Sandy. I feel so bad for her.
-还不如单身一人呢  -是吗
- Well, it's better than being alone. - Is it?
她看过来了
She's looking over here.
-我的天呐 -米奇尔  你坐到按钮了
- Oh, my god. - Mitchell, you're sitting on the button.
什么  我没有  没坐到
What? No--no, I'm not. No, I'm not!
它卡住了
The--it's stuck!
最后一次是你用的
And you're the one that had it last
-你用它向奶酪店喊话  -因为啊
- when you were talking to the cheese shop! - Because you know what?
如果你要推销松露奶酪
If you advertise truffle cheese,
-就要抓住顾客的期望  -你好啊  桑迪
- there are certain expectations... - Hi, Sandy.
我代表克莱尔・邓菲致电给您
Yeah, I'm calling on behalf of Claire Dunphy.
-多美的名字啊  -她曾是普通百姓
- What a beautiful name. - She used to be a citizen.
我代表镇议会候选人克莱尔・邓菲致电给您
I'm calling on behalf of Claire Dunphy for town council.
好  要不这样吧
All right. How about this?
如果你投票给克莱尔・邓菲
if you vote for Claire Dunphy...
你这辈子都不用交税了
You won't have to pay taxes for the rest of your life.
投克莱尔一票
Vote for Claire!
卢克  你这是干嘛
Luke! What are you doing?
你不能这么说
You can't say that!
政客都是这样的
Oh, like she'd be the first politician
竞选承诺向来不用兑现
to make a promise she can't keep.
是吗  也许我也不想跟你说话
Well, maybe I don't want to talk to you, either.
也许是你在烦我
Maybe you are the one that is bothering me!
你觉得好受不
How do you like that? Eh?
歌洛莉亚  我得再次提醒你
Gloria, I'm gonna have to ask you again
请照着稿子读
to please stick to your script.
可是每个人都拒绝我
But everybody's saying no to me!
我搞不懂
I don't get it.
平时我叫别人干嘛
Usually when I ask someone to do something,
别人就干嘛
they just do it!
也许是因为那些人通过电话无法看到你的美貌
Maybe it's because these people can't see you.
我不喜欢
I don't like it.
你不能给我弄个视频电话吗
Can't you just hook me up to some sort of camera?
谢谢你  麦琪  谢谢支持
Well, thank you, Maggie, for the vote.
好的  再见
Okay. Bye-bye.
请坐在这儿
Here's your seat.
谢谢  请原谅
Thank you. Um, you'll have to excuse me.
我有点儿紧张  我从没上过电台
I'm a little nervous. I've never been on the radio before.
别担心
Don't worry about it.
-就当是聊天好了  -好的
- Just think of it as a conversation. - Okay.
这是耳机  音量控制
Here are your headphones. Volume control.
-别离麦克风太远  -好的
- Don't get too far from the mike. - Okay.
请确认手机关闭
Make sure your cell phone's off.
哦  关掉手机  对...
Oh. Cell phone. Right. Um...
确认下你没在嚼口香糖  对吧
And you're not chewing gum, are you?
没  我没在  只是刚做了些临时性的
No, I'm not. I just had some temporary
牙科类小手术
dental work done.
最后我只需要...
The last thing I need--
欢迎回到《时事记录》
And welcome back to "A matter of record."
我是希瑟・范・甘迪
I'm Cecil Van Gundy.
今天来到演播室的是来自43区的
Joining us now in studio is district 43
镇议会候选人克莱尔・邓菲
town council candidate Claire Dunphy.
谢谢  希瑟
Thank you, Cecil.
很高兴能参加这个节目
It's a pleasure to be here.
那么...你本次是首次参选
So... You're a first-time candidate.
跟大家说说你是怎么有这个念头的
Tell us what got you involved.
一切都始于一个...
It all started with a, um...
一个停车标志
With a stop sign.
我忧心于我家周围的街道安全
I was concerned about safety in our neighbourhood
并且我没有从市政厅得到满意的答复
and I was not getting any satisfaction from city hall.
老妈是抽什么风了
What's wrong with mom?
哦  这下可不妙
Oh, this isn't good.
她听起来跟醉了一样
She sounds drunk!
你是没听过她喝醉后的声音
That's not her drunk voice.
再说说咱们镇上存在的其他问题吧
Tell us about some of the other issues facing our town.
你对本市针对污水和可持续发展的
Where do you stand on the city's
倡议提案持什么样的观点
sewage and sustainability initiative,
就是所谓的"污持案"
the so-called S.S.I.?
如果我们要讨论
One cannot really talk about
"淤"...淤水和可持续发展的问题
s-s-sewage and sustainability
就不得不先探讨...循环利用的问题
without first discussing... recycling.
政府方面可以做得更多...
This city can do more...
-她是想闹哪样  -针对循环利用问题
- What the hell's wrong with her? - with the recycling program...
跟喝醉了一样
She sounds drunk!
-当前...  -都是牙给闹的
- ...currently... - It's a tooth thing.
怎么了
What's wrong?
氧气快吸完了  天啊
Oh, I'm almost out of air. Oh, boy.
那很要紧吗
Is that serious?
你觉得氧气要紧吗
Is oxygen serious?
说实话  帮你取眼镜耽误了我大把时间
You know what? I lost a ton of time getting your glasses.
我还是把你丢家里吧
I'm just gonna drop you at home.
你能好好吸氧  我也好去接其他人
You can get your air. I can drive other people.
我家里没有多余的氧气瓶了
I don't have any more tanks at home.
怎么会  你要学会未雨绸缪啊
Why? That seems like bad planning.
我忘记再多订点了
Well, I forgot to order them.
服的药总让我很健忘
My pills make me forget things.
哦  靠  我该吃药了
Oh, shoot! I gotta take my pill!
你别告诉我你药也忘带了
Please tell me you have it with you.
当然带着了  但我必须和食物一起服下
Of course I do, but I have to take 'em with food.
-是的吧?  -你问我我问谁去
- Don't I? - Are you asking me?
对的  我就是和食物一起服下的
Uh, yes! I do take them with food!
哦  我感觉不大好
Ooh. I don't feel so well.
好的  你要什么我都给你弄来
Okay, I'll get you whatever you want!
给你去搞氧气  给你去搞食物
I'll get you the air, I'll get you the food.
然后我去给你的醉媳妇儿投上一票
Then I'll vote for your drunk wife.
那可不是她酒醉的声音
That is not her drunk voice!
非常感谢你参与投票
Thank you so much for voting.
非常感激
We appreciate it.
嗨非常抱歉打扰下  我是杰・普里契特
Hi. I'm terribly sorry. Excuse me. Jay Pritchett.
能不能让我速战速决
Uh, can I get in-- in and out really quick?
谢谢  给张选票就成
Thank you. This is all I needed.
非常感谢  非常感谢
Thank you very much. Thank you very much.
好的  克莱尔  克莱尔  克莱尔
All right. Claire, Claire, Claire.
克莱尔  克莱尔  在这里
Claire, Claire-- ahh, ahh. Here.
抱歉  抱歉  抱歉
I'm sorry! I'm sorry, I'm sorry!
好啊  多蒂
Hello, Dottie!
杰  见到你可真开心
Jay! It's so nice to see you!
-是吗  -哦  为什么不开心
- Is it? - Oh, why wouldn't it be?
都是陈年旧事  过眼云烟了
That was a long time ago. Water under the bridge.
-没关系的  -哦  那就好
- We're good. - Oh, that's great.
非常感谢你参加投票
Thank you so much for voting.
还记得我女儿克莱尔吗  她现在...
You remember my daughter Claire. She's--
正在参选镇议会议员
She's running for town council.
-哦  真是不错啊  -我真为她骄傲
- Oh, isn't that neat? - Yeah, I'm so proud.
你该把选票放进去吧
So you're gonna put it in there, huh?
是啊当然  当然要放进去
Oh, yeah, of course. Yeah. Definitely.
每一票都很重要  是吧
cause every vote counts, you know.
非常感谢你能参与投票
Thank you so much for voting.
-我说...  -是啊
- You know... - Yeah.
天啊  我要亲眼看到我这宝贵的
Boy, I'd sure like to see the sweet sight
一票...计算在内
of my vote... counting.
我为什么要许诺某事却不履行呢
Why would I say I'd do something and not do it?
我这不就成了个骗子了嘛
That would make me a liar...
我只是个容易轻信别人的寡妇
instead of a trusting widow
曾经睡倒在一个男人温暖的怀抱中
Who fell asleep in the warm embrace
他可答应我  要给我做早餐呢
of a man who promised to make breakfast.
很好  该来的躲不掉
Okay, here it is.
听着  我十分抱歉
Look, I am so sorry.
和前妻离婚后你是我遇到的第一个女人
You were the first woman I'd been with besides my ex--
35年的婚姻
35 years.
我慌了手脚
I panicked.
我倒不是说你脱光了就不漂亮
An-and it wasn't 'cause y-you weren't pretty naked
或者类似的什么原因
or anything like that.
我要躲着安琪・迪金森啊
I'd have run from Angie Dickinson.
-哦  她可真幸运  -多蒂
- Oh, lucky her. - Dottie--
-回见  杰  -多蒂  多蒂  拜托
- Good-bye, Jay! - Dottie, Dottie, please.
我就是想把我的票塞进"洞"
I'm just trying to get my ballot in the box.
果然还是老样子
oh, yeah, that sounds familiar.
恩  都不用麻烦你做什么
Yeah, but you don't have to do anything.
让我自己把它"插进去"
Just let me put it in!
我这话听起来真别扭
Uhh. Shouldn't have said that.
我们实在太对不起了
We are so sorry.
我们不是故意让你听到那些话的
We did not mean for you to hear any of that.
对  其实
Yes, and you know what?
我们一开始就不该八卦你的
We shouldn't have been gossiping in the first place.
万一你们是对的呢
But what if you're right?
格雷戈里就是个同性恋怎么办
What if Gregory is gay?
我妈跟我说过  我没敢信她
When my mom said it, I didn't believe her.
毕竟她住在爱荷华[允许同性婚姻]
She lives in Iowa.
不过要是你们也这么认为
But coming from you two!
-完全证明不了什么  -对
- Means nothing. - No.
我们对你的未婚夫一无所知
We barely know your fiance.
-他说自己是直男  他就是  -直男
- If he says he's straight, he's straight. - Mm. Straight.
我们下个月就要结婚了
We're getting married in a month.
人们都往这儿赶来了
People are flying in.
他为我俩报了舞蹈课
He signed us up for dance classes.
哦  天啊
Oh, my god!
别  不要这样  嘿
No. No, no, no. Hey.
-基佬就爱这样  -对
- This is what gays do. - Yeah.
-喜欢聊八卦  -大聊特聊
- We gossip. - We gossip a lot.
他也爱八卦
He gossips!
不是的  你没理解我的意思
No. No. You're missing the point, okay?
每当我们看到像格雷戈里那样的美男子
We see a great-looking guy like Gregory,
就会说他是基佬  因为我们希望他是
and we say he's gay because we want him to be gay!
-是吗  你们确定吗  -是这样的
- Really? Really? Are you sure? - Yes. Yes.
就是这样  见过我们怎么对待影星吗
Absolutely. Look at what we do with movie stars.
对
Okay.
知道吗  休・杰克曼  他又会唱又会跳
You know? Hugh Jackman-- he sings, he dances,
真是梦中情人
He's dreamy!
很明显我们特想他与我们站在"同"一战线
So obviously we would want him on our team!
-对  -但他就是个直男
- Yeah. - But he's straight.
相信我  我很清楚的
Trust me, I know.
有一次我在餐厅里跟他打招呼
I said hello to him once in a restaurant,
那一刻我嗅不到丝毫的基情
and there was absolutely no chemistry.
是啊  说到这份儿上你要还不信...
Well, if that isn't proof...
三个星期后  桑迪和格雷戈里结了婚
Three weeks later, Sandy and Gregory got married,
每个人都说那婚礼美极了
and everyone said the wedding was beautiful.
那些花可都是格雷戈里布置的
Gregory did the flowers....
对于一个直男来说  其实一点都"不奇怪"
Which is perfectly normal for a straight guy.
希腊人就一件事做得靠谱  就这羊肉
The Greeks do one thing right, and it's lamb!
好了  咱赶紧去投票吧
All right. Let's go vote.
你家媳妇儿哪根经搭错了非要跑去当政客
Why the hell does your wife want to be a politician, anyway?
她不刚说过  她就想在布里斯托路和
You heard her. She wanted to put up
绿叶路那放块停车标志
a stop sign at Bristol and Greenleaf,
然后她遇到...
But then she ran into--
等等  慢着
Wait, wait, wait!
我住的地方就离那不远
That's near where I live!
对啊  我们是邻居呢  走吧
Yeah. We're neighbors. Let's go!
我才不会给这事投票呢
No way I'm voting for that!
政府已经管得太宽了
Too much government already.
我为国上战场可不是为了让政客来告诉我
I didn't fight a war so some politician
我该在哪个地方停车
could tell me where I have to stop my car.
你根本就不开车
You don't even drive!
那是因为奥巴马那家伙把我驾照吊销了
That's 'cause that Barack Obama took my license away.
我可不觉得那事跟他有关
I don't think he was involved in the decision!
我今天出门是要给我老婆拉到50票的
I left the house today to get 50 votes for my wife.
我才不要一票都没有就回家
I'm not going home with zero.
你至少能帮帮忙  走进去
The least you can do is walk right in there
替我家媳妇投上一票
and punch a hole for the woman
她每周二都帮你把垃圾桶推上车道啊
who drags your garbage can up your driveway every Tuesday!
我不喜欢  那跟我的全部信仰都背道而驰
I don't like it! Goes against everything I believe in.
是吗  就一个停车标志
Really? A stop sign?!
不过我会去的  因为你是个好孩子
But I'll do it, 'cause you're a good kid.
我今天原本过得也还不错
And I had a nice day...
直到你冲我吼了起来
till you started yelling at me.
十分抱歉  谢谢你了
So sorry. Thank you.
走吧
Here you go.
告诉你  我老婆以前也是个酒鬼
You know, my wife was an alcoholic, too.
好吧  投个票而已
Okay. Let's just go vote.
那是老兵政治记者
That's veteran political reporter
沃特・夏皮洛
Walter Shapiro.
大家好啊
Hi, everyone!
-有什么新闻吗  -还没  还没
- Any news? - Not yet, not yet,
不过即使我输了  至少我知道
But even if I lose, at least now I know
我在播音界还是有点前途的
I have a future in radio.
我就不行  人得要看见我的脸才行
I couldn't. People need to see me.
在拿到结果之前  我想要感谢你们大家
Before we get the results, I just want to thank you all
感谢你们为我做的所有事
for everything you've done for me.
米奇和小卡  谢谢你们一整天
Mitch and Cam, for campaigning for me all day
开着你们的"克莱尔号"为我竞选
in your little Claire-mobile.
-那是我们至少可以做到的  -对
- It's the least we could do. - Yeah.
是真的"少"
Literally.
我们为休・杰克曼的电影做的宣传
We probably did more for Hugh Jackman's career
可能都比为克莱尔做的多
than we did for Claire's.
还有曼尼和歌洛莉亚
And, Manny and Gloria,
谢谢你们打了那么多电话
thank you for making all those phone calls.
还有  爸爸
And, dad...
谢谢你的支持
for all your support.
我觉得我没有说服一个人为克莱尔投票
I don't think I convinced anyone to vote for Claire.
我自己好像都没投上票
I don't think I even voted.
还有我老公
And my husband...
四处开车
who drove around
送了不知道多少位老人去投票
I don't know how many senior citizens today to the polls.
一位
One.
还有我可爱的孩子们
And my beautiful children,
是你们的信念让我有信心
whose faith has given me the confidence
相信我可以做到
to believe that I can do this.
我可以
I can--oh.
-谁来接  我输了  -妈妈  妈妈
- Somebody else answer it. I lost. - Mom. Mom.
-我可以感觉得到  -妈妈
- I can feel it. I-- - Mom.
你可以的  妈妈  接电话吧
You can do it. Mom. Answer the phone.
你好
Hello?
我就是
This is she.
谢谢你打电话通知我
Thanks so much for calling.
再见
Bye-bye.
有个坏消息
I have some bad news.
因为你当上议员要变忙了吗
Because someone's gonna be busy now that she's a councilwoman?
不  我没有在跟你们开玩笑
No, no, I wasn't doing that fake thing.
-我真输了  我输了  -不是吧
- I really lost. I lost. - Ay, no.
真遗憾  不过  你知道吗
I'm so sorry. But you know what?
我们都还是非常为你骄傲
We are still just so proud of you.
我不知道你们怎么想的
Yeah! I-- I don't know about you,
反正  我要喝一杯酒
But, um... I could use a glass of wine.
现在你们能听到她喝醉的嗓音了
Ohh. Now you're gonna hear her drunk voice.
妈妈
Mom?
你还好吧
You okay?
是的  好着呢
Yes. Fine. I'm good.
我很好  我不好  我是想赢的
I'm fine. I'm not fine. I wanted to win,
然后  我现在很尴尬
And... and I'm so embarrassed.
外边所有人都为我而努力
I mean, everybody out here worked so hard for me,
都信任我
and they believed in me,
而我让他们失望了
and I let 'em down.
亲爱的
Oh, honey.
乖女儿
Oh, sweetheart.
别哭啊  我会没事的
Well, don't cry. I'm gonna be fine, sweetie.
真的  我会没事的
Really, I am.
知道你这么在乎  我就已经好多了
Just knowing you care so much makes me feel better.
不是  我收到4封拒信
No, I got four rejection letters
一直没告诉你们
I never told you guys about.
什么
What?
加州圣巴巴拉分校  俄勒冈  威斯康辛
I got rejected from U.C.S.B., Oregon, Wisconsin...
-不是吧  -还有西北大学的
- Oh, no. - And Northwestern.
那一个我们是有点高攀了
Well, we were overshooting on that one.
那那个
What about, uh...
今天收到的  最后的机会了
It came today. My last chance.
我不敢打开
I'm too scared to open it.
无论它怎么说
Whatever it says in there,
你爹和我都超级为你自豪
your father and I are crazy proud of you.
好吗
Okay?
我今年真的有开始努力
I did start trying this year.
我知道的  你努力了
I know you did. You did.
没有什么好羞耻的
You have nothing to be ashamed of.
你也一样
Neither do you.
还是有点不一样的
It's a little bit different.
不  其实完全一样
No, it's exactly the same.
不同的是  你一直都很努力
Except you tried really hard the whole time,
而不是临时抱佛脚
not just at the end.
你说的对
You're right.
是一样的
It is the same.
我们没什么可感到羞耻的
We have nothing to be ashamed of...
一起把它打开吧
So let's open that together.
对  打开吧
Yeah, open it.
什么  不行  你们在这儿干吗
What? No! What are you doing here?
来嘛海莉  我们都相信你
No. Come on, haley. We believe in you.
开封吧
Do it!
实在没学校要  就来给我打工
You can always work for me.
来吧  你可以的  你可以的
Come on. You can do it. You can do this.
-来吧海莉  -好吧
- Come on, Haley. - All right.
打开  打开  打开  打开
Open. Open, open, open.
亲爱的邓菲小姐
"Dear Miss Dunphy,
我们很遗憾地通知你
We regret to inform you..."
宝贝儿
Oh, honey.
虽然我们现在不能给你入学通知
"While we cannot offer you admission at this time,
但你是很棒的候选人  因此
"You are a promising candidate, and therefore
我们很乐意将你放在候选名单中
We would like to place you on our wait list!"
我的天  我进候选名单了
Oh, my god, I got wait-listed!
我们收下了
We will take it!
太好了
Yeah!
恭喜啊  恭喜啊
Congratulations! Congratulations!
我们女儿可能要去上大学了
Our daughter might be going to college!
菲尔  看
Phil, look.
一个停车牌
A stop sign.
写着你收
It's addressed to you.
亲爱的克莱尔  我赢了  你输了
"Dear Claire, I won. You lost.
收下你傻兮兮的停车标志
"Here's your stupid stop sign.
下次要想来烦扰我
"Next time you think about bothering me,
请也"停止"吧
"Please take its advice.
议员  可敬的杜恩・贝利敬上
Your councilman, the honorable Duane Bailey."
亲爱的  你做到了
Honey, you did it!
我做到了
I did it.
我让邻里变得更安全了
I made our neighborhood a little bit safer.
我搞不好已经救了人命了
I may have even saved life.
你个傻缺  有停车标志呢  你不识字吗
You idiot, there's stop sign! Can't you read?
我们需要减速带
we need speed bumps.
不不  不行  亲爱的
No, no. No! Honey!
corrected by yth796